A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (L-Z), Accession 2021:051 FA1790
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Community and National Initiatives, 2001-2017; 1
  - She Can Win - Leadership Development Program (2016-52344) (Box 54, Folder 704)
  - Shorebank Enterprise Detroit dba Detroit Development Fund - Small Business Technical Assistance Program (2014-50084) (Box 54, Folder 706)
  - Silicon Valley Community Foundation - On the Table, Silicon Valley (2017-53761) (Box 54, Folder 708)
  - Silicon Valley Bicycle Coalition - Bikepool San Jose (2015-51554), 2013-2016 (Box 54, Folder 709)
  - Silicon Valley Bicycle Coalition - Open Streets (2014-48611) (Box 54, Folder 710)
  - Silicon Valley Community Foundation - Regional Media Collaborative, 2016 Knight Community Information Challenge (KCIC) Reinvestment (2016-53249) (Box 54, Folder 711)
  - Silicon Valley Community Foundation - Giving Day Initiative, San Jose/Silicon Valley (2013-47038), 2011-2014 (Box 54, Folder 712)
  - Silicon Valley Community Foundation - Spreading the Word (2013-47333), 2011-2015 (Box 54, Folder 714)
  - Silicon Valley Community Foundation - Supplemental Grant to Donor Advised Fund (2009-0270), 2009-2017 (Box 55, Folder 715)
  - Silicon Valley Talent Partnership - Local Innovation, Local Challenges (2014-45388), 2011-2016 (Box 55, Folder 717)
  - Singularity Education Group - Global Impact Competition, Miami (2014-48572), 2012-2015 (Box 55, Folder 720)
  - Small Business Opportunity Center, Inc. - East Little Havana Businesses with Storefront Improvements and Code Compliance (2003-0255) (Box 55, Folder 721)
  - Smart Growth America - Amazing Place Study Tour (2016-53261), 2014-2017 (Box 55, Folder 722)
  - Smart Growth America - Local Leaders Council (2014-48311), 2011-2014 (Box 55, Folder 723)
  - Social Swag Company - 2014 Social Good Summit Miami (2014-48973), 2012-2014 (Box 56, Folder 726)
  - Social Venture Partners Charlotte - SEED20 (2012-2452), 2012-2015 (Box 56, Folder 727)
  - The Solo Project - Designing the Solo City of the Future (2014-50191), 2014-2015 (Box 56, Folder 732)
  - Sourcemap, Inc. - Farm-to-Table Traceability Platform (2012-0203) (Box 56, Folder 739)
  - South Dakota Community Foundation - Dakotafire Media, Knight Community Information Challenge (2011-0132), 2009-2014 (Box 57, Folder 740)
  - South Dakota Community Foundation - Supplemental Grant to Donor Advised Fund (2009-0252), 2009-2016 (Box 57, Folder 742)
  - Southeast Asian Mutual Assistance Association Coalition, Inc. - The Vendor Villiage in the Park: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54182) (Box 57, Folder 743)
  - Southminster - Cycling Without Age, Charlotte (2017-54415) (Box 58, Folder 756)
  - Springboard for the Arts - Can Can Wonderland (2016-52992) (Box 58, Folder 760)
  - SPUR - Urban Transformation of San Jose (2014-49349), 2012-2017 (Box 58, Folder 762)
  - SPUR - Diridon Station Study Tour (2017-54006) (Box 58, Folder 763)
  - SPUR - Regional Strategy for the Bay Area (2017-54010), 2015-2017 (Box 58, Folder 764)
  - Space Fund NFP, The Rebuild Foundation - ArtHouse: A Social Kitchen (2015-50699), 2012-2015 (Box 58, Folder 765)
  - Startup Angels, Inc. - AngelSummit Americas (2015-51280) (Box 59, Folder 774)
  - Stow-Munroe Falls Public Library - Technology Upgrades and ADA Compliance (2009-4564) (Box 59, Folder 778)
  - Steven Babitch Design, LLC - Building and Engaging Detroit through Human-Centered Design (2015-51179), 2013-2015 (Box 60, Folder 779)
  - Street Plans - Miami-Dade Quickbuild Program: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54228) (Box 60, Folder 783)
  - Street Plans, University of Akron Foundation - Exchange Street Demonstration Project (2017-54754) (Box 60, Folder 784)
  - Street Plans - Tactical Urbanist's Guide to Materials and Design Workshops (2016-52775), 2013-2016 (Box 60, Folder 785)
  - Street Plans - Tactical Urbanist's Guide to Materials and Design (2015-51547), 2013-2015 (Box 60, Folder 787)
  - Strong Women, Strong Girls - Skills Development for High-Risk Girls, Miami-Dade County (2011-0091), 2011-2013 (Box 60, Folder 788)
  - Studio Gang Architects, Ltd. - Studio Gang Civic Commons (2015-51950), 2013-2015 (Box 60, Folder 790)
  - Summit Cycling Center - Akron Innerbelt Bicycle Park: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52483), 2014-2017 (Box 60, Folder 791)
  - Summit Education Initiative - Increase Career Certificates and Post Secondary Degrees (2015-50408) (Box 60, Folder 792)
  - Summit Series LLC - Summit at Sea x Knight Foundation Scholarship Program (2016-52761), 2013-2016 (Box 61, Folder 794)
  - Sustain Charlotte - Bicycling for All (2017-55307) (Box 61, Folder 797)
  - SV@Home - Supporting Housing Ready Communities (2017-55350) (Box 61, Folder 798)
  - Sweat Equity Enterprises Inc. - Enstitute Miami Hub (2014-48744), 2012-2014 (Box 61, Folder 799)
  - Tallahassee-Leon County Cultural Resources Commission - The Longest Table (2016-52521) (Box 62, Folder 809)
  - Teach for America Inc. - Startup Summer (2015-50429) (Box 62, Folder 813)
  - Teach for America Inc. - Teach for America Miami-Dade (2009-0194), 2007-2016 (Box 62, Folder 814-815)
  - Team Better Block - International Hostel on Airbnb (2015-50675) (Box 62, Folder 817)
  - Tech Cocktail, LLC - Tech Cocktail, Miami (2013-47162), 2011-2013 (Box 63, Folder 821)
  - TechGirlz Charitable Foundation - Digital Learning Workshops at Free Library Branches (2017-54375) (Box 63, Folder 822)
  - Technically Media, Good Company Group, Inc. - Tech in the Commons: Nonprofit Tech Tools Bootcamps (2017-53906) (Box 63, Folder 824)
  - Technology Affinity Group - 2014 Conference, Miami (2014-49023) (Box 63, Folder 830)
  - Technology Affinity Group - General Operating Support (2007-0027) (Box 63, Folder 831)
  - Technology Foundation of the Americas Inc. - eMerge Americas (2014-49846), 2012-2016 (Box 63, Folder 832)
  - Tech Museum of Innovation - Civic Innovation Spaces (2014-49749), 2012-2015 (Box 63, Folder 833)
  - TechShop San Jose, LLC - Knight Placemaking Lab (2016-52098), 2013-2016 (Box 63, Folder 834)
  - Temple University - Urban Apps and Maps Studio (2012-0229), 2010-2013 (Box 64, Folder 840)
    Opportunities for black and Latino residents to join Philadelphia's growing apps development community.
  - Third Sector New England, Inc. - Jane's Walk (2015-50877), 2015-2017 (Box 64, Folder 847)
  - Tides Foundation - The Campaign for Grade-Level Reading (2017-53991) (Box 65, Folder 856)
  - Torchbearers - Empowerment Initiative (2014-50169), 2012-2014 (Box 65, Folder 861)
  - Transit for Livable Communities - ReConnectRondo (2016-53494) (Box 66, Folder 865)
  - TreesCharlotte - Low-Income, Under-Treed Neighborhoods (2017-55001) (Box 66, Folder 866)
  - TreesCharlotte - Expanding Resident Engagement (2015-51454), 2013-2016 (Box 66, Folder 867)
  - Trustees of the University of Pennsylvania - Fels Institute of Government's Public Policy Challenge (2013-43339), 2010-2013 (Box 67, Folder 888)
  - Trustees of the University of Pennsylvania - Community Development Fellows (2005-0133), 2005-2008 (Box 68, Folder 889)
  - The Trust for Public Land - Environmental Assessment of Akron's Summit Lake (2016-53435) (Box 68, Folder 890)
  - The Trust for Public Land - Park at Griggs Street (2016-52953) (Box 68, Folder 891)
  - Tubman African American Museum, Inc. - Back Lot Drive-In at the Tubman: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54179) (Box 68, Folder 892)
  - Twin Cities Innovation Alliance - Innovation and Design Center (2017-55286) (Box 68, Folder 896)
  - Twin Cities Public Television (TPT) - Living for the City: A REWIRE Initiative (2017-54895) (Box 68, Folder 897)
  - Twin Lakes Library System - The Year of Voting Dangerously: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54547) (Box 68, Folder 898)
  - Twin Lakes Library System - The Democracy Lab, A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52510) (Box 68, Folder 899)
  - UK Citizens Online Democracy - Technical Assistance for First-Time Government Engagement (2012-3593) (Box 68, Folder 901)
  - United States Artists, Inc. - Knight Community Artists (2009-0117), 2007-2014 (Box 69, Folder 903)
  - United Way of Central Carolinas, Inc. - Unite Charlotte Fund (2016-53545) (Box 69, Folder 904)
  - United Way of Central Georgia - Read2Success Community Engagement Campaign (2016-52819) (Box 69, Folder 905)
  - University City District - Just Spaces Tool (2017-54143) (Box 69, Folder 909)
    A citywide audit tool in Philadelphia to assess public spaces to better understand their equitable, inclusive use and accessibility.
  - University of Akron Foundation - Education Recruitment for African American Men (2010-0193), 2008-2014 (Box 69, Folder 916)
  - University of Chicago - Propagating Community Transformation through Community Engagement (2014-48163), 2011-2016 (Box 70, Folder 919)
  - University of Detroit, Mercy - Partnering with the City and Neighborhoods to Enhance Design Impact (2015-51803) (Box 70, Folder 920)
  - University of Florida - Bob Graham Center for Public Service (2010-0298), 2010-2014 (Box 70, Folder 924-925)
  - University of Miami - The New Miami: Its Transformation since the 1990s, Alejandro Portes (2016-52559) (Box 71, Folder 935)
  - University of Miami - Third Place Project (2014-49889), 2014-2016 (Box 72, Folder 942)
  - University of St. Thomas - I'm Going to Vote Today!: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52518) (Box 74, Folder 963)
  - University Park Development Corporation - University Park, Akron (2012-1916), 2010-2012 (Box 75, Folder 972-973)
  - Urban Land Institute - Plan to Life in Akron Conference (2017-54760) (Box 75, Folder 977)
  - Urban Us Public Benefit Corporation - Smart City Startups 2015 and 2016 (2014-49338), 2013-2015 (Box 75, Folder 978)
  - Urban Us Public Benefit Corporation - Smart City Startups (2013-47463), 2012-2014 (Box 75, Folder 979)
  - Van Alen Institute: Projects in Public Architecture - The South Florida Challenge: Innovation in the New Climate Economy (2016-53340) (Box 76, Folder 984)
  - Varian Shrum - Your Move, Charlotte: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54292) (Box 76, Folder 985)
  - Veggielution - Eastside Grange, San Jose (2016-53161) (Box 76, Folder 986)
  - Venture for America Inc. - Charlotte Selection Day (2017-53879) (Box 76, Folder 987)
  - Venture for America Inc. - Miami Program (2016-52140), 2016-2017 (Box 76, Folder 988)
  - Venture for America Inc. - Miami Expansion (2015-50387), 2013-2015 (Box 76, Folder 989)
  - Venture for America Inc. - Miami Expansion (2014-48051), 2012-2014 (Box 76, Folder 990)
  - Venture Scout US Corporation - Startup Bootcamp (2015-51020), 2015-2017 (Box 77, Folder 991)
  - Visit Macon - Destination Health (2017-55192) (Box 77, Folder 999)
  - Waccamaw Community Foundation - Giving Day Initiative, Myrtle Beach (2013-47121), 2011-2015 (Box 77, Folder 1006)
  - Waccamaw Community Foundation - Supplemental Grant to Donor Advised Fund (2009-0268), 2009-2016 (Box 78, Folder 1007-1008)
  - Warren-Conner Development Coalition, Inc. dba Eastside Community Network - Expanding Digital Literacy at the Neighborhood Level (2017-54991) (Box 78, Folder 1013)
  - Warren-Conner Development Coalition, Inc. dba Eastside Community Network - Community-led Vacant Land Management Pilot Project (2015-50700), 2015-2016 (Box 78, Folder 1014)
  - Warren-Connor Development Coalition, Inc. dba Eastside Community Network - Resident Engagement Training Curriculum (2015-51816), 2015-2016 (Box 78, Folder 1015)
  - Wayne State University - Research and Writing of Detroit's Grand Bargain (2015-51253) (Box 79, Folder 1021)
  - Wayne State University - Citizen Detroit (2014-49955), 2011-2017 (Box 79, Folder 1022)
  - Welcoming America Inc. - Welcoming Cities (2014-49433), 2012-2016 (Box 79, Folder 1023)
  - Welcoming Center for New Pennsylvanians - Skilled Immigrant Career Pathways Program (2014-48593), 2013-2015 (Box 79, Folder 1025)
  - The Well Community Development Corporation - Middlebury Community Development Corporation (2017-54670) (Box 79, Folder 1026)
  - West Palm Beach Community Redevelopment Agency - The Sunset Rises Again: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52511) (Box 79, Folder 1030)
  - West Side Community Land Trust - Capacity Building (2017-55103) (Box 79, Folder 1031)
  - WhereByUs, Inc. - Startup Miami 2.0 (2016-53085), 2013-2016 (Box 80, Folder 1035)
  - WhereByUs, Inc. - Local Civic Engagement (2014-50159) (Box 80, Folder 1036)
  - Wichita Community Foundation - Innovation Center (2009-0275), 2006-2014 (Box 80, Folder 1039)
  - William Marsh Rice University - Local Elections in America Project (2015-50864), 2013-2016 (Box 80, Folder 1043)
  - Women's Network Inc. - Women's Network of Northeast Ohio (2016-52124), 2016-2017 (Box 81, Folder 1050)
  - Women of Tomorrow Mentor and Scholarship Program - Philadelphia, Detroit, and Palm Beach Expansion (2010-0299), 2009-2017 (Box 81, Folder 1051-1052)
  - World Education Services - Mapping the Trajectories of Immigrant Professionals in Six U.S. Cities (2014-49137) (Box 82, Folder 1054)
  - Wynwood Yard, LLC - Community Events and Programming (2017-53866), 2014-2017 (Box 82, Folder 1058)
  - Wynwood Arts District Association (WADA) - Accelerated Start-Up for Wynwood Business Improvement District (2013-46789), 2012-2014 (Box 82, Folder 1059)
  - Yerba Buena Center for the Arts - People's Award: Market Street Prototyping Festival (2016-53208) (Box 82, Folder 1063)
  - Young Nation - Elsmere-Avis Plaza Project (2016-52393) (Box 82, Folder 1065)
  - YouthBuild USA - Alumni Leaders Program (2013-42803), 2011-2015 (Box 82, Folder 1066)
- Journalism and Media Innovation, 2002-2017; 2
  The Journalism and Media Innovation program focuses on protecting freedom of the press and free speech, as well as advancing methods of journalism that impact local media, and promotes talent, leadership, and technology innovation.
  - Latino Public Radio Consortium - Restore Public Radio Communications to Puerto Rico (2017-55116) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund - API to Expand Access to Nonpartisan Election Information (2015-51551), 2013-2016 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Institute for Journalism in New Media, LLC - Newsroom Digital Transformation Project (2016-53342), 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - LION Publishers - Local Independent Online News Publishers Peer-to-Peer Learning Network (2016-53331) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Lonely Goat Media - Resources for Women in Media Innovation and Entrepreneurship (2012-0324) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Long Beach Community Foundation - Journalism Conference (2016-53534) (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Lost Light Projects Inc. - Inside Climate News Sponsorship Project (2015-50876), 2014-2016 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Louisiana State University - Social Media News Challenge (2013-47533), 2012-2015 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - LoudSauce, Inc. - Louder (2014-48498), 2012-2014 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Crowd-funded advertising to extend the reach of journalism that is important to audiences.
  - MapBox LLC - OpenStreetMap (2012-2093), 2012-2013 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Market Atlas - Market Atlas (2014-49109), 2012-2014 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    To understand journalistic approaches to collecting data in remote geographies by prototyping a system to crowdsource microeconomic data from Africa.
  - Marshall Project Inc. - Journalism Engagement (2016-53291), 2016-2017 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Massachusetts Insititute of Technology - Capture, Analyze, and Visualize Election Conversations (2015-51373), 2014-2017 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - CrossCloud and Social Dev Kit (2014-48536), 2012-2015 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    Open source software that allows users to store their data outside applications and increase their mobility and privacy.
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - MIT Media Lab (2014-48697), 2013-2017 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - W3C20 Symposium (2014-49158), 2014-2016 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    A symposium to celebrate the web as an open platform for free expression.
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - DOG Programming Language (2013-46918), 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - 2013 MIT-Knight Civic Media Conference (2013-46920), 2012-2014 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Matthew Terenzio - Project Fission (2014-48412), 2012-2014 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    Prototype application to test the use of small, structured information units in narrative storytelling.
  - Max Ogden - Small Data (2013-46305), 2011-2013 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Media and Place Productions - Zeega Publisher and Community Growth (2013-46784), 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Media and Place Productions - Zeega (2011-0282), 2008-2012 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    An HTML-5 based toolkit to encourage collaborative multimedia project publishing.
  - Media Development Loan Fund, Inc. - Legal Representation for Bloggers and Digital Journalists (2011-0085), 2011-2012 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Meedan Inc. - Checkdesk: An Open Verification Toolkit for Journalists in the Digital Age (2014-49094 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - MetaLayer, Inc. - Abayima and openSIMkit (2012-0404), 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    Tools for distributing and publishing information via SIM cards in situations where communication networks are comprimised.
  - Miami Foundation - 2017-2018 Fund for Nonprofit News (2017-54295), 2014-2017 (Box 13, Folder 166)
  - Miami Foundation - Journalism 360 Immersive Storytelling Challenge (2016-53600) (Box 14, Folder 193)
  - Miami Foundation - Supplement Knight Advised Fund (2016-53609), 2013-2016 (Box 15, Folder 195)
    To preserve First Ammendment rights in the digital age.
  - Miami Foundation - Supplement Knight Advised Fund (2016-53691), 2016-2017 (Box 15, Folder 197)
    Focus on communities, journalism, technology innovations and arts as a means of developing informed and engaged communities.
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Foundation Advised Fund (2014-50201), 2012-2014 (Box 18, Folder 227)
  - Miami Foundation - Newsroom Innovation Fund (2013-47821), 2013-2014 (Box 20, Folder 248)
  - Miami Foundation - Local Media Initiative (2013-47764), 2012-2013 (Box 20, Folder 249)
  - Miami Foundation - News21 (2011-3054), 2009-2012 (Box 21, Folder 258)
  - Michigan Nonprofit Association - ConCENSUS (2013-47656), 2011-2014 (Box 23, Folder 276)
  - Michigan Suburbs Alliance - On Board (2014-49064), 2012-2015 (Box 23, Folder 277)
  - Michigan Suburbs Alliance - On Board (2013-46310), 2011-2013 (Box 23, Folder 278)
  - Middle Tennessee State University Foundation - Studio M (2015-50982), 2015-2017 (Box 24, Folder 284)
  - Mike Tigas - Tabula (2014-48497), 2011-2014 (Box 24, Folder 285)
    A PDF data-scraping tool.
  - Mikva Challenge Grant Foundation Inc. - Expunge.io: Youth-Driven Solutions to Juvenile Record Expungement (2014-48416) (Box 24, Folder 286)
  - Minnesota Public Radio - Project Carbon, National Public Radio (NPR) (2015-51355), 2013-2017 (Box 24, Folder 294)
  - Minnesota Public Radio - American Public Media Health Initiative (2013-47257), 2012-2014 (Box 24, Folder 295)
  - MinnPost - Building A Better CRM-CMS Connector (2016-53515) (Box 25, Folder 297)
  - MinnPost - Memberships (2014-48224), 2011-2015 (Box 25, Folder 298)
  - MLRC Institute - Media Law Training for Journalists (2016-53310) (Box 25, Folder 303)
  - MLRun - MLRun (2014-48408) (Box 25, Folder 304)
    Machine learning algorithms to discover patterns in documents and networks.
  - Montclair State University Foundation - Social Media Best Practices, FB Journalism Project, Local News (2017-53750) (Box 25, Folder 308)
  - Morgan State University - Baltimore Reporting Project (2016-52388), 2016-2017 (Box 25, Folder 309)
  - Mozilla Foundation - New York Times and Washington Post Project (2014-48550) (Box 25, Folder 312)
    To build a user-generated content and commenting platform that empowers users and creates a community.
  - Mozilla Foundation - Knight-Mozilla Partnership (2013-46738), 2010-2016 (Box 26, Folder 313)
  - Mozilla Foundation - User-Generated Content System (2014-48699), 2012-2017 (Box 26, Folder 314)
  - MuckRock Foundation Incorporated - MuckRock (2016-53728) (Box 26, Folder 315)
  - MuckRock LLC - Connections Crowdsourcing App and Infrastructure (2014-49640), 2012-2015 (Box 26, Folder 316)
  - Natalie Cadranel - PressSecure (2014-48513), 2012-2014 (Box 27, Folder 231)
    Application to securely archive citizen media while preserving metadata needed for authentication.
  - National Association of Black Journalists - NABL Student Multimedia Journalism Projects (2016-52729), 2016-2017 (Box 27, Folder 333)
  - National Association of Black Journalists - Conference Sponsorship (2014-49066) (Box 27, Folder 334)
  - National Association of Broadcasters - PILOT Innovative Change (2016-53181), 2013-2017 (Box 27, Folder 335)
  - National Association of Hispanic Journalists - Puerto Rico Emergency Communications Access and Journalism Initiative (2017-55118) (Box 27, Folder 340)
  - National Association of Hispanic Journalists - Student Multimedia Newsroom Projects (2016-52765), 2013-2017 (Box 27, Folder 341)
  - National Conference of Editorial Writers Foundation - Minority Writers Seminar (2004-0239), 2005-2010 (Box 28, Folder 345)
  - National Freedom of Information Coalition - Strengthening State FOI and First Amendment Rights (2017-54334) (Box 28, Folder 348)
  - National Freedom of Information Coalition - Press Freedom and Freedom of Information (2009-02320), 2009-2013 (Box 28, Folder 353-354)
  - The National Geographic Society - Slow Journalism Event (2014-49599), 2011-2015 (Box 29, Folder 355)
  - The National Geographic Society - Out of Eden Walk (2014-49723), 2012-2016 (Box 29, Folder 356)
  - National Institute on Money in State Politics - Follow the Money (2014-48149), 2011-2015 (Box 29, Folder 358)
  - National Public Radio - Project Carbon (2013-43177), 2010-2015 (Box 29, Folder 363)
  - New Mexico Community Foundation - Searchlight New Mexico Data Portal (2016-53069), 2016-2017 (Box 30, Folder 378)
  - New Michigan Media - Detroit Journalism Cooperative: Ethnic Community Engagement (2016-53499), 2016-2017 (Box 30, Folder 380)
  - New Michigan Media - Detroit Journalism Cooperative (2014-50239), 2014-2016 (Box 30, Folder 381)
  - The New School - Journalism and Design (2014-48571), 2012-2015 (Box 31, Folder 384)
  - The New School - Journalism and Design Expansion (2016-53099), 2015-2016 (Box 31, Folder 393)
  - Newseum Inc. - Promoting Free Expression on College Campuses (2016-52106) (Box 31, Folder 385)
  - Newseum Inc. - First Amendment Center, John Seigenthaler (2014-49448) (Box 31, Folder 386)
  - Newseum Inc. - Public Awareness of Journalism and the First Amendment (2008-0025), 2008-2017 (Box 31, Folder 387-389)
  - News Revenue Hub, Inc. - Building Capacity for News Match and Beyond (2017-54634) (Box 31, Folder 390)
  - Newstap.es - NOD: News on Demand (2014-48428), 2012-2014 (Box 31, Folder 391)
  - The News Literacy Project, Inc. - Virtual Classroom (2016-52892), 2013-2017 (Box 31, Folder 394)
  - New Venture Fund - Solutions Journalism Network (2014-47981), 2011-2014 (Box 32, Folder 398)
  - New York Public Radio - On the Media (2017-53815) (Box 32, Folder 406)
  - New York Public Radio - Project Carbon (NPR) (2015-51386), 2013-2015 (Box 32, Folder 409)
  - New York Public Radio - Discover App Feature (2014-49619), 2012-2015 (Box 32, Folder 410)
  - New York University - Member-Supported Journalism (2016-53710), 2016-2017 (Box 32, Folder 413)
  - NextDrop - Water Services Notification System (2011-0277), 2011-2012 (Box 33, Folder 421)
  - North Central Texas Council of Governments - Neighborhood Crime Watch Software (2012-2343), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 431)